Reading books [music] of different
entrepreneurs is one of the best hacks
to get yourself out of the rut because
every entrepreneur or even every person
has been in different periods of life
where there are ruts. And the [music]
reason why entrepreneurship books are
really good because these are success
stories, right? Like
>> [music]
>> there are people who just getting stuck
in a rut and they stay there. And what
you want to learn from are people who
have gotten stuck [music] in a rut and
have gone out of it. Biographies are
very useful thing. Podcasts are also
very useful thing, but I find that it's
it's a lot harder to find podcasts that
are inspiring than books. Like there's
there's kind of a greater filter for
books. Some books I would recommend is
like Total Recall, uh which is Arnold
Schwarzenegger's biography. Also Ride of
a Lifetime, uh that's Bob Iger's
biography. Like he was like a intern at
one of the lowest positions at Disney
and he rose up to becoming the CEO. And
the biography from Walter Isaacson I
also would recommend it.